本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
喔唷  查莉  快看你圆滚滚的西瓜肚
Uh-oh, Charlie, look at your tummy.
看来有人吃了太多的煎饼吧  不许再吃了
I think somebody's had enough pancakes. No no.
哎呀我的天
Oh my goodness,
看来有人太爱她的小毯子了
Somebody loves her blankie.
变出来了
Whoo!
好啦  老爸  现在该拉出你的毯子了
All right, dad, now pull out your blankie.
当然可以了  儿子
Sure thing, son,
等我把你送到军校去之后再说
Right after I drop you off at a military school.
哎呀  快看这礼拜六是什么日子
Oh, hey, look what's gonna happen on Saturday.
啊对了  旧货店的捐贈车会过来
Oh, yeah, the truck from the thrift store is coming.
根本就是你们的结婚周年纪念日好不好
And it's your wedding anniversary.
对哦
Right.
那捐赠车几点来啊
What time is the truck coming?
那你们今年到底要怎么庆祝嘛
So how are you guys gonna celebrate this year?
最好的庆祝方式就是能报税少一点
There's no better way to celebrate than the tax deduction.
（注：加美税策用于慈善事业款可以得到退税）
所以我们要去捐献旧衣服
We're gonna get from donating old clothes.
老公  还记得我们结婚十周年的时候减了多少税吗
Bob, remember the deduction from our 10th anniversary?
强大啊
Ooh!
兄弟们  兄弟们  你们看这样行不
Guys, guys, guys, you know what?
我觉得我们得给爸妈的周年纪念日好好策划一下
I think we should do something for mom and dad on their anniversary.
我们在母亲节父亲节做的还不够多吗
Don't we do enough for them on mother's and father's day?
你根本啥也没做过吧
You never do anything for them.
谁说的  正是我的出生才让他们成为了父亲母亲
Excuse me, I was born, which made them a mother and a father.
我的使命算是完成了
My work is done.
那个  我想啊  我们可以给他们制造一次浪漫的惊喜晚餐
Well, I think. We should surprise them with a romantic dinner.
你也会做晚餐吗
You're gonna make a dinner?
那好  我是说我们要给他们惊喜
I think we should surprise them.
以预订浪漫晚餐的方式也行
And order a romantic dinner.
然后我们可以做服务生伺候他们啊
Then we can serve it to them like waiters.
为什么女生的点子总是要我们干很多活
Why do girl ideas always take so much work?
我懂了
I get it.
只要我们好好伺候他们
If we do something nice for them,
他们就也能给我们很多好处
They have to do something nice for us.
好比会买礼物给我们呀  说的对
Like give us presents.  Yes.
为啥你们就不能想着是因为我们要恪守孝道呢
Why can't we just do it because we love them?
因为那样啥也得不到呀  笨阿姐
Because then we don't get stuff. Duh.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
Today's all burnt toast
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
Running late, and dad jokes
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
Has anybody seen my left shoe
■
翻译： 山鹰逢羽
我闭上双眼  咬口早餐
I close my eyes, take a bite
跳上车子  放声大笑
Grab a ride, laugh out loud
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
There it is up on the roof
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
I've been there, I've survived
所以请听取我的建议
So just take my advice
■
校订  后期： WaitinZ
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, baby,
世界有很多疯狂无奈
Things are crazy
可是我知道你会有美好未来
But I know your future is bright
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
不要怀疑
There is no maybe
一切终会如你所愿
Eveything turns out all right
生活有悲有喜
Sure life is up and down
可是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
But trust me, it comes back all around
你会喜欢将来的你
You're gonna love who you turn out to be
宝贝  不要放弃
Hang in there, Baby
查莉成长日记  第一季第十四集
Good Luck Charlie  S01E14  Blankie Go Bye Bye
喂  你们
Hey!
总该有人去叫查莉闭嘴吧
Shouldn't someone go tell Charlie to shut up?
我看还是你再去试试吧
You know what? You give it a shot.
我们都哄了她一晚上了
We've been trying all night long.
说到我们  他指的只有我自己而已
And by "We" He means me.
谁说的  我也起来了一次的
Come on, I got up that one time.
你起来冲厕所  又把她吵醒了
And when you flushed, you woke her up.
可这孩子为啥这么闹心啊
But why is she so fussy?
我们找不到她的小毯子了  到处都找过了就是没有
We can't find her blankie. And we've looked everywhere.
哎呀  真是可笑
Oh, that's ridiculous.
她也不能总是要抱个东西才能睡着吧
She shouldn't need something to help her sleep.
你不也有个绒毛猴子么
What about your stuffed monkey?
小可可是不一样的
Coco's different.
爸妈  这样过你们的周年庆也太磕碜了
Guys, what a horrible way to spend your anniversary.
你们要准备出门了
We should really get out of the house.
哎哟  你干嘛打我呢
Ow. What are you doing?
哦对了
Oh.
爸爸妈妈  在你们的周年纪念日这一天
Mom and dad, on your anniversary
我要带你们去外面下馆子还有看电影
I'm taking you to lunch and a movie,
算我招待你们
My treat.
哦  老爸  别忘了带钱包
Oh, dad, bring your wallet.
儿子你不明白“招待”那个词是什么意思吧
You don't know what "My treat" Means, do you?
好了  孩子们  我们是很想去看电影
Okay, we'd love to go to a movie, kids,
但也不能在查莉这么烦心的时候
But not when Charlie's so upset.
我会找到查莉的小毯子  照顾好她的
I'll find Charlie's blankie and take care of her.
现在你们俩就出去好好享受一下独处时光吧
Now you two go out and enjoy some alone time.
在你们的周年纪念日这天
On your anniversary.
还要带着盖比
With Gabe.
我还知道该看什么最赞的影片呢
And I know the perfect movie to see...
《星球大爆炸二部：行星命运倒数》 3D效果唷
"Star Exploders II: Ticking Asteroids" in 3D.
嘿  知道不  评论家都不喜欢那电影
Hey, you know what? The critics hated that.
那一定就很好看了
That means it's gotta be good.
没错呀
Oh, yeah.
或者呢  我们可以去看《为明天哭泣的杨柳》
Or we could see "The Willow Weeps Tomorrow."
那部讲的啥
What's that about?
述说了一个少女的传奇人生
It's a haunting tale of a young girl.
她是一个农家姑娘  种了一棵杨柳树
Who lives on a farm, plants a willow tree.
之后她怀着成为一个芭蕾舞者的梦想渐渐成长
And grows up with dreams of becoming a ballerina.
然后在最重要的一次试演时
And then on the day of the big audition.
她扭伤了脚踝  只好回到农场去
She twists her ankle, goes back to the farm,
结婚生子
Gets married and has a baby.
你知道她给孩子取了什么名字吗
And do you know what she names it?
叫杨柳啊
Willow.
我感觉已经看完这电影了
I feel like we just saw it.
味同嚼蜡啊
And hated it.
行行好吧  男子汉们  结婚纪念日也有我的一半啊
Oh, come on, guys. It's my anniversary too.
不是这个意思  你说的很对
No no no, you're absolutely right.
要么  我们现在先别决定吧
Look, we don't have to figure this out now.
等到了电影院再想要看什么好了
We'll decide when we get to the theater.
也行
Okay.
行了吧
一定要看《星球大爆炸》
"Star Exploders"!
查莉  我这不是在找你的毯子吗  求你别哭了
Charlie, I'm looking for your blankie. Please stop crying.
哎呀快看  开始放你最喜欢的节目了哟
Oh, look, it's your favorite show...
“圈圈”节目呀  是那些会唱歌的五颜六色的圈圈哟
"The circles. " They're the colorful singing shapes.
会教你各种各样的  圈圈
That teach you about shapes.
我是一个红圆圈  我就是圈圈
I am a red circle, yes, I am
我又大又圆又红呀
I am big and round and red.
耶
Hey!
晕  这太吵了
Man, this is annoying.
哦  看我找到啥了  这是你的小毯子吧
Oh, what's this I found? Is this your blankie?
看来你不满意呀
I'll take that as a no.
不如我带你去散散步吧
Let's take you on a walk.
一定能让你好受些
That'll make you feel better.
耶
Yay!
借过
Excuse me.
真妙  看来我是万绿从中一点红啊
Great, I think I'm the only woman in here.
不尽然吧  那不也是个
Hey, what about...?
啥也不是
Nope.
我有点饿了
I'm kind of getting hungry.
说得对  我们吃点东西吧
Yeah, you know what? Let's eat.
拿去给你爸
Pass this to your dad.
这也太强了吧
Isn't this great...
根本不用去买电影院的食物
Not having to buy that movie theater food?
我们省了不少钱哟
We're saving so much money.
跟我本来想像的略有不同
I guess I had a different picture in my mind.
一开始盖比说的不是“午餐和电影”组合么
When Gabe said "Lunch and a movie."
我记得他说的是“边吃边看”呀
I think he said "Lunch in a movie."
妈妈  你有没有帮我带奶昔呀
Mom, do you have my milkshake?
喔
Oh.
看来这样更简单
You know what? I think it's easier.
不如你把管子插在这儿自己吸吧
If you just stick the straw in.
哎呀  电影开始了
Hey, the movie's starting.
不会吧
Really?
劳驾  你能把你那触手给摘了吗
Excuse me, could you take off your tentacles?
我拿到蛋糕啦
Got the cake.
哇  这都弄的什么呀
Whoa. What's all this about?
这是今晚主宴的主题布景呀
Oh, it's the theme for tonight's dinner.
我把客厅改造成了摩洛哥宫廷风
I turned the living room into a moroccan palace.
我们要伺候他们吃摩洛哥食物吗
So we'll be serving moroccan food?
那不会让老爸肚胀气吗
Won't that make dad gassy?
随便取个国家名又不会让老爸胀气的
Name a country that won't make dad gassy.
说的对啊
Good point.
你还在找查莉的小毯子吗
Are you still looking for Charlie's blankie?
哪儿都找不到啊
I can't find it anywhere.
我想是不是被我放在脏衣服篮里了
I thought I put it in that pile of dirty clothes.
我们还有个放脏衣服的篮子吗
We have a dirty clothes pile?
对呀  每次你把它们随便扔在地板上时
Yeah, it's where your clothes magically go.
就是那玩意儿可以将你的脏衣服神奇变消失
After you throw them on the floor.
但愿你没把它扔在捐献篮里
I hope you didn't put it on the donation pile.
要是捐给旧货店  那可就扔的太远找不回来了
For the thrift store, 'cause that is long gone.
我们把她的小毯子给捐掉啦
We gave her blankie away?
是你捐掉了她的小毯子
You gave her blankie away.
我们必须去找回来
We have to get it back.
是你自己必须去找回来
You have to get it back.
你别那样说话啦
Stop saying that.
你自己别说啦
You stop saying that.
哈哈  一般都是我在家捣蛋惹事的
You know, I'm usually the one who messes things up.
可是这次我这边操控的一切
But this time everything on my side of the operation.
全部运作良好  看吧
Is going just fine. See?
“祝艾丝达和马蒂一路平安”
"Bon voyage, Esther & Marty"?
咦
Oops.
你带错蛋糕回家啦
You brought home the wrong cake.
我们能不能告诉爸妈说
Can't we just tell mom and dad.
这个“一路平安”在法语里其实是“结婚纪念日快乐”的意思
That "Bon voyage" Is french for "Happy anniversary"?
那这人名“艾丝达和马蒂”怎么算
What about "Esther & Marty"?
谁管他们呢  那俩人都上船旅游去了
Who cares about them? They're on a ship.
行了  在爸妈回来之前我们还有一些时间
Okay, we still have time before mom and dad get home.
我们可以整好这些乱子的
We can fix this.
怎么整啊
How?
你开车把我放在旧货店那儿
You drop me off at the thrift store.
我去找回毯子的时候你就去换蛋糕
I'll grab the blankie while you go switch cakes.
我们快去吧
Let's do it.
还得带着查莉一起去才行呀
Let's do it with Charlie.
哇
Oh!
唷
Yeah!
太赞了
That was awesome.
山寨的吧
And derivative.
他们在《太阳骑警：星际探索者四》里已经这样搞过了
They did it in "Solar Troopers: Star Quest IV."
在这电影放完前到底要炸多少个星球啊
How many stars have to explode before this thing is over?
一万三百六十五个
10, 365,
我听他们在聊天室里说的
Or so they said in the chat room.
妈妈  你能晃晃你的手袋吗
Hey, mom, could you jiggle your purse?
我的奶昔都结块了
My shake's clogging.
亲爱的  把你的手机关了吧  那样太吵了
Honey, put your phone away. It's distracting.
在3D版的银河系大毁灭场景下  你还嫌我的手机太吵吗
My phone is distracting from the 3d destruction of the milky way?
请别吵好吗
Do you mind?
你自己还不是在说话
You were talking too.
为了电影欢呼  这是完全合理的
About the movie, which is totally allowed.
合理是吧
Oh, yeah?
亲爱的  亲爱的  你要去哪儿啊
Honey, honey, where are you going?
我要出去
Out.
劳驾  你能挪一下你的鳍脚吗
Excuse me, could you move your flipper?
我应该去找他谈谈
I should go talk to her.
总统先生
Mr. President,
只有您能下令引爆这颗超新星
Only you can give the order to explode the supernova.
愿银河系原谅我的罪过
May the galaxy forgive me.
哇塞
Whoo!
劳驾  劳驾
Excuse me, excuse me.
你好  我捐了个东西  现在想要回去
Hi, I donated something and I have to get it back.
又来了
Oh, dear.
有些人就是搞不懂“捐献”的意思
Someone doesn't know what the word "Donation" Means.
我跟你说啊  小可爱  这叫覆水难收  捐物不回
See, darling, when you "donate" something, you "do not" get it back.
你不明白那对我们有多重要
You don't understand how important this is.
我不小心把我小妹妹的宝宝毯给捐出去了
I accidentally gave away my baby sister's blankie.
你家小妹妹的宝宝毯哦
Your baby sister's blankie?!
关我鸟事
I still don't care.
你是不是有起床气呀
Did someone wake up on the wrong side of the bed?
我是睡沙发的  我妈才睡的床
I sleep on the futon. Mama gets the bed.
你能不能帮我啊
Can you help me?
我看我也没办法
I'm afraid it's out of my hands.
这星期捐来的所有物资都已经堆在那卡车上要运走了
Everything that was donated this week is already on that truck.
莱斯利洗狗店为您服务
Leslie's dog-washing service.
要是你的狗狗脏兮兮  我可让它恢复柔顺滑亮
If your pooch is dirty, I'll make him purty.
兼职工作  我还是个生存教练
Side business. I'm also a life coach.
可以啊  好的
Yeah, uh-huh.
哎呀  我好像看到了
Oh, I think I see it.
不行  夫人  我们不洗猫的
No, ma'am, we don't wash cats.
猫自己会洗澡
Cats wash themselves.
啊哦
Uh-oh.
等等  别开车啊  别啊
Wait, no. Hold it, no.
哔哔哔
Boop boop boop!
这是茄香酱  库斯米面酱
This is zaalouk, couscous,
羊肉锥炖锅  千层派  传统浓汤
Tajine, pastilla and harira.
还有问题吗
Any questions?
我还真有个问题  你的真名真的是阿齐兹吗
Actually, I do have a question. Is your name really Aziz?
这是在礼拜六的五点到九点时的名字
It is on saturdays between 5:00 and 9:00.
礼拜二和礼拜四  我就是南美高乔饭店的拉乌尔
Tuesdays and thursdays I'm Raoul from El Gaucho.
真酷呀
Oh, cool.
我也做快餐店的工作
I'm also in the food delivery business.
我在咕唧鸡店上班
I work for Kwikki Chikki.
就是那些带着个大公鸡头帽子的人吗
You mean the guys who wear the rooster hat.
还有个特别卡通的鸟嘴的
With the cartoon beak?
兄弟  你还有自尊吗
Where's your pride, man?
我得接一下电话
Gotta answer the phone.
喂
Hello.
PJ哥
PJ
泰迪  你怎么回事呀
Teddy, what happened to you?
我回去那旧货店的时候  你根本不在那
I went to the thrift store and you weren't there.
我被关在卡车厢里头了
I'm locked in the back of a truck.
哇  这件很靓嘛
Ooh, this is cute.
怎么还有人把这扔了呢
Someone threw this out?
说啥呢  泰迪  我听不到
What? Teddy, I can't hear you.
你走出去看看信号能不能好点
Try going outside to get better reception.
要是我走的出去  我也不用给你打电话求救了
If I could go outside, I wouldn't have to call you.
那好  我有主意了  不如我走出去好了
Okay, I have an idea... why don't I go outside?
现在能听到了吗
Can I hear you now?
我被关在卡车的后车厢里了
I'm locked in the back of a truck.
为啥被关在卡车里呀
Locked in the back of a truck?
泰迪  你怎么会这么笨的
Teddy, how could you be so stupid?
呃  当我没说  我先挂了
Um, forget that question. I gotta go.
别挂啊  喂  别挂
Wait, no. Wait, no.
呃  对了
Um, yeah.
小查莉啊
Charlie, hi.
你能不能给我开门呀
Can you open the door for me?
乖乖  到这边来  查莉  你要跑到哪里去呀
Charlie, come here. Charlie, where are you going?
查莉  查莉
Charlie, Charlie.
查莉  你倒是过来呀
Charlie, can you come here?
好姑娘  再靠过来一点  再近一点
Thattagirl. A little closer. A little closer.
查莉  天呐  别动那些食物啊
Charlie, no. No, not the food.
查莉求你了  到我这里来
Charlie, please. Please come here.
查莉  查莉  喂  喂
Charlie, Charlie, hi, hi.
过来  过来
Come here. Come here.
对  好姑娘  好姑娘
Yes, thattagirl. Thattagirl.
再过来点  再过来点
A little closer. A little closer.
晕
Ugh.
你本事那么大  怎么就不能开个门呢
You can do that, but you can't open the door?
亲爱的  你错过了整场电影啊
Hey, honey, you're missing the whole movie.
是啊  我根本就不想看
Yeah, that's kind of the idea.
那你们怎么也出来了
What are you doing out here?
那个长触角的男的尽放屁呢
The guy with the tentacles cut the cheese.
对  就是那个长触角的人放的
Yeah, it was the guy with the tentacles.
亲爱的  你怎么不高兴了
Honey, what's wrong?
我不晓得
I don't know.
我想如果我们能在结婚周年日这天更多地纪念一下会更好
I guess the truth is it would be nice to do more on our anniversary.
以前我们都会特意庆祝的
We used to do special things.
现在却在这儿吃我带在手袋里的洋葱圈
Now we're eating onion rings out of my purse.
你还带了洋葱圈哦
There were onion rings?
可是我以为我们以前说好了
But I thought we agreed
以后不用特地去庆祝什么
we weren't gonna do anything special.
是啊  我知道  我知道说好的
Yeah, I know. I know we did.
那你现在还是希望要有庆祝活动吗
So now you want to do special things?
呃  总比无所事事的好
Well, it's better than doing unspecial things,
像是坐在一群四十岁的宅男中间看电影这种事还是算了
Like sitting in a theater full of 40-year-old nerds.
喂  我才三十六呀
Hey, I'm only 36.
好了  不如这样
Okay, you know what?
你们回去继续看那电影吧
You guys go back and enjoy your movie.
我就去看《为明日哭泣的杨柳》好了
And I'm gonna go see "The Willow Weeps Tomorrow."
别  亲爱的  等一下  等一下
No, honey, wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute.
你要吃那洋葱圈不吃
Are you gonna want the onion rings or...?
你拿去吃吧
Here you go.
结婚纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary.
我觉得这事儿没搞对啊
I don't think I handled that very well.
你觉得呢
Ya think?
哦天呀
Oh, man.
我真应该事先计划一下的
I should have planned something.
好吧  也许你有后续计划哦
Well, maybe you did.
你说的是什么意思
What do you mean?
其实哥哥姐姐和我给你们准备了惊喜
Well, Teddy, p. J. And I are surprising you guys.
是一个周年纪念晚宴呢
With an anniversary dinner.
都是我的主意哦  没泰迪什么事儿
It was all my idea, not Teddy's.
可是我可以把功劳让给你啦
But I can let you take the credit.
你说真的吗  你这孩子为了我做的
Are you serious? You'd do that for me?
当然可以了  只要把这人情记到盖比日的那天
Sure. Just remember me on Gabe's day.
盖比日是什么东西
What's Gabe's day?
我就等着你给我惊喜了
Surprise me.
哎呀我的吗  一只手臂
Agh! An arm!
我的老天呀  现在的人还真是什么都敢捐
My goodness, people will donate anything.
帮我一下吧
A little help here.
你在我的卡车厢里面干什么啊
What are you doing in the back of my truck?
在找我妹的小毯子啊  可是没找到
Looking for my sister's blankie. And it's not in here,
不过我找到一件很靓的背心  看哪
Although I did find this really cute top, see?
你知道怎么穿它最合适吗
You know what would look good with that?
滚出我的卡车去
Get out of my truck!
可我根本不知道身处何处啊
But I don't even know where I am.
你在我家的车道前
You're in the driveway of my house.
我妈最喜欢在这些旧衣服里淘第一手金
Mama always likes first dibs on my pile.
等等  那她还让你睡沙发哦
Wait, and you still have to sleep on the futon?
那样可不太公平吧
That just doesn't seem right.
你能不能帮我去跟我妈讲
Would you mind telling that to my mama?
查莉  开下门好吗
Charlie, please open the door.
啊  窗户开着呢
Open window.
哈哈  我来喽  查莉
Ha ha! Coming, Charlie.
真是伤感啊
This is so sad.
我知道
I know.
她先是失去了男人
First she loses her man,
现在又失去了嗅觉
And now her sense of smell.
她的问题就是她付出了太多的爱
Her problem is she loves too much.
我觉得这片能得奥斯卡
I smell Oscar.
可是她自己没有奖拿呀
But she won't.
你们来干啥
What are you doing here?
我当然是担心你咯
I was worried about you.
再说我们那部电影放完了
And our movie ended.
哎哟
Ow!
听着  亲爱的  我本来不想告诉你的
Look, honey, I wasn't gonna tell you this,
不过我其实在家安排了一个惊喜纪念等着你呢
But I've got an anniversary surprise waiting for you at home.
真的吗  你准备了啥
Really? What is it?
如果我告诉你了  就一点不惊喜了  对吧
If I told you, it wouldn't be much of a surprise now, would it?
哦
Oh.
我爱你
I love you.
谢谢你能留下来陪我看完这场电影
Thanks for staying and watching the rest of the movie with me.
呃
Oh.
好吧
Okay.
我干嘛也要留下来啊
Why do I have to stay?
要是你不留下来呢  盖比日就要取消了
Because if you don't, Gabe's day is canceled.
你跑到这个厅来看什么啊
What are you doing here?
我是智慧与心灵并重的
I have a heart as well as a brain.
我可不是没有情感的机器人呀
I'm not a robot.
其实我希望自己是
I wish I was.
老爸啊  你想不想换个座儿
Hey, dad, do you want to switch seats?
我离开了百老汇舞台
So then I left Broadway.
挥一挥衣袖  不带走半片云彩
I've never looked back.
我真不敢相信自己仍然没找到查莉的小毯子
I can't believe I didn't find Charlie's blankie.
我敢发誓
I could have sworn
我已经把那卡车厢翻了个底朝天了
I looked at every single thing in that truck.
你到底有没有听我述说我的人生故事啊
Were you even listening to my life's story?
你连皮特·鲁鲍的事都没兴趣吗
Does the name Patti lupone mean nothing to you?
（注：美国著名百老汇歌手）
对不起啦  我只是
I'm sorry, I just...
你坐在屁股下的那个是什么啊
What are you sitting on?
只是一块小毯子呀
Just a little blanket.
不是吧  那个就是查莉的宝宝毯啊  快给我
No, that's Charlie's blankie. Give me that!
拿去吧
Oh, there.
你干嘛垫着它坐呀
Why were you sitting on it?
怎么说呢
How shall I put this?
我有一种病状叫做后位汗腺疏松症
I have a medical condition known as posterial hydrosis.
那是啥意思
What's that?
就是屁股老出汗
Butt sweats.
恶
Eww.
好吧  不过还好我找回它了
Well, at least I got it back.
天呐  快停车  倒回去
Stop the truck. Back it up.
哔哔哔
Boop boop boop!
好了  在我们进家门前我想先跟你说
Okay, look, before we go in I just want to say something.
我知道自己不是那种很罗曼蒂克的男人
Now I know I'm not always the most romantic guy,
但我总该做一次  因为这是你应得的
But I should be, because you deserve it.
结婚纪念日快乐
Happy anniversary!
惊喜哦
Surprise!
哎呀  小查莉
Oh, Charlie.
出什么事啦
What happened?
问老爸吧  这些全是他一手包办的
Ask dad. He planned the whole thing.
为了你们的纪念日  我们愿意为您们献上
For your anniversary we'd like to serve you
一场传统摩洛哥盛宴
a traditional moroccan feast.
不过因为酒宴都被打翻了
But since that ended up on the floor,
所以我们带来了
we bring you...
花生酱吐司
Peanut butter toast.
你们这些孩子真是乖巧
This is so sweet of you kids.
知道不  我觉得最后这还是成为了
You know, I think this turned out to be
一次很美好的纪念日呢
a pretty great anniversary after all.
我都不介意自己正坐在库斯面酱上了
I don't even mind that I'm sitting in couscous.
现在是演出时间啦
And now it's time for the entertainment.
女士们  先生们  容我为大家介绍
Ladies and gentlemen, may I present to you...
邓肯家舞蹈团
The dancing Duncans!
是不是很奇妙啊  就这一片布
Isn't it amazing how a little piece of cloth
也能让一个人这么开心
can make someone so happy,
即使那上面都是卡车轮胎味还有别人屁股上的汗
Even when it's covered in tire tracks and butt sweat?
我会在你睡着后帮你洗了它的啦
I'm gonna wash it after you fall asleep.
不过最好笑的是  因为我们都这么依恋自己的小毯子
But it's so funny, because we love our blankies so much,
可是总有一天根本就把它全忘在脑后
And then one day we forget all about them.
如果你像姐姐我的话
And if you're like me,
大概到五岁的时候就不再需要它了哦
you'll grow out of yours by the time you're five.
晚安
Good night.
可要是你是像你小哥盖比
But if you're like Gabe,
那我琢磨着你大概要一直带着它去度蜜月也有可能
You might bring it on your honeymoon.
祝你好运啰  小查莉
Good luck, Charlie.
喂  我有点饿了呀
Hey, you know what? I'm kind of hungry.
把这个递给你爹
Pass this your dad.
还有别的吗
Anything else?
我昨天吃过炸鸡了呀  有没有别的
I had chicken yesterday. Got anything else?
咦  没有配菜吗
What, no fixings?
耐心点
Hold on.
哎  亲爱的  你自己不吃点啥吗
Hey, honey, aren't you gonna have something?
哦  我差点忘了
Oh, I almost forgot.
为你效劳
Okay,
谁点了墨西哥烤玉米片
Who ordered nachos?
是我点的
That would be me.
嘘  轻声
Shh.